allegiantdeals.com 2011-05-25

# Privacy Policy | Travel Is Our Deal™ | Airfare & Hotel Packages from Allegiant

Allegiant Air is concerned about your right to privacy. When you visit the Allegiant Air website, you can be assured that any information you share with us will be treated confidentially. The only instances that would require us to disclose Customer information (i.e. - name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, etc.) is under legal subpoena, to verify billing information with the Customer's financial institution, credit card fraud detection or other valid law enforcement requests. In addition, from time to time, we may market certain third party services through our site. Should you choose to accept an offer from a third party, we will pass your relevant personal information, including your name, postal address, email address and your credit/debit card number, to that third party.

"The Transportation Security Administration (TSA) requires you to provide your full name, date of birth, and gender for the purpose fo watch list screening, under the authority of 49 U.S.C. section 114, the Intelligence Reform and Terrorism Prevention Act of 2004 and 49 C.F.R parts 1540 and 1560. You may also provide your Redress Number, if available. Failure to provide your full name, date of birth, and gender may result in denial of transport or denial of authority to enter the boarding area. TSA may share information you provide with law enforcement or intelligence agencies or others under its published system of records notice. For more on TSA privacy policies, or to review the system of records notice and the privacy policy impact assessment, please see the TSA website at [www.tsa.gov](http://www.tsa.gov/)."

**E-mail addresses**  
Email addresses provided by you to Allegiant Air shall not be shared with any third parties that are not contractually obligated to a relationship with Allegiant Air or Allegiant Travel.

**Security**  
We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) 128 bit encryption on your personal information. This keeps the data that you send to Allegiant Air private and secure. This technology ensures the safety of transmitting personal information over the internet.

The VeriSign Secure Site Seal assures our online customers that the Allegiant Air website has been authenticated by VeriSign and that confidential transactions with Allegiant Air website are secured by SSL encryption.

**Policy Changes**  
Allegiant Air reserves the right to modify its Privacy Policy at any time. In the event that we make a material change to our policy we will post a notice of the change on this page.

**More Questions?**  
If you still have questions about our privacy policy, please visit our Contact Us page for different options on how to reach us.
